字幕翻译&制作 真喜
一切是从桥上开始的
It starts on a bridge.
克雷格!
Craig!
你打算怎么处理你的自行车,亲爱的?
What were you planning to do about your bike, hon?
我才不管什么自行车呢 我要自杀
I don't care about my bike. I'm killing myself.
但这辆车很贵的,老兄
But we spent a lot of money on the bike, sport.
我们唯一的要求就是让你爱护它
We only ask that you take care of it.
为我想想,克雷格 我长大了说不定要骑呢
Think of me, Craig. I might want that bike when I grow up.
对不起 我没想到这些...
I'm sorry. I just didn't think it...
没错 在你决定这么做的时候
That's right. You just didn't think about us
你就是不考虑别人,是吧,亲爱的?
when you were deciding to do this, did you, honey?
要我说,确实挺自私的
Pretty selfish, I'd say.
你想过这会对你妹妹产生什么影响吗?
Have you thought about how this might affect your sister?
我很...抱歉,我...
I'm... I'm sorry, I...
这就是通常我在恶梦中惊醒的时刻
This is the moment where I usually wake up in a sweaty panic.
但是由于某些原因,
But for some reason,
这次有些不同
this time was different.
说来有点可笑
周日
我...
I...
我想要自杀
I want to kill myself.
先填这个
Fill this out.
嘿
How you doing?
有烟吗?
You got a cigarette?
没,抱歉
No, sorry.
你有什么毛病?
What's wrong with you?
我就是不抽烟
I just don't smoke.
不,我是说,你星期天早晨五点跑急诊室来干吗?
No, I mean, why are you in an ER, at 5:00 on a Sunday morning?
这个...
Well...
就是最近有点焦头烂额
I guess, there's just been a lot going on in my mind lately.
继续说
Go ahead.
不太好解释
Okay, well, this is sort of difficult to explain.
有一个女孩...
But... See there's this girl...
啊,明白了
Yeah, got you.
还有暑期学校的申请,让我一直很紧张
And this summer school application that I'm really nervous about.
暑期学校?
Summer school?
是的,很有名的一所暑期学校
Yeah, it's like this super prestigious, kind of...
你暑假为什么想呆在学校里?
Why would you want to be in school in the summer?
你应该到科尼岛上去追小妞才对
You should be on Coney Island, bird-dogging chicks.
你是医生吗?
Are you a doctor?
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
你...你看起来可不太像个医生
You... You don't really seem like a doctor.
听说过杜奇豪瑟吗?
You ever heard of Doogie Howser?
总而言之,不管你有什么问题 希望他们都能治好你
Well, I hope they fix whatever's wrong with you.
谢谢
Thank you.
你产生自杀的念头有多久了?
So, how long have you been feeling suicidal?
我也不清楚 我已经抑郁了差不多一年了
I don't know. I've been depressed for about a year.
我之前也有过这种念头,但从没像现在这样
And I've thought about it before, but never like this.
从没这么强烈
You know, never so real.
最近有什么特别的事情让你有了这种感觉吗?
Did anything happen today specifically to trigger these feelings?
有时我真想 为自己抑郁的原因找个容易回答的答案
Sometimes I wish I had an easy answer for why I'm depressed.
比如我爸打我 或者我被性侵犯
That my father beat me. Or I was sexually abused.
但我的问题却没有那么夸张
But my problems are less dramatic than that.
比如,我爸总是问我无厘头的问题
Like, my dad always asks the wrong questions.
克雷格,华尔街的面试怎么样?
So, Craig, how's the Intro to Wall Street class?
也许这看上去有些夸张,
So maybe this is a slight exaggeration,
但是我一紧张就容易呕吐
but I do have a problem with stress vomiting.
有时朋友看我的表情 就像我是火星人一样
And my friends sometimes look at me like I'm from another planet.
而且我迷上的这个女孩
And I'm obsessed with this girl.
恰巧是我死党的女朋友
Who happens to be going out with my best friend.
所以,有让我想轻生的原因吗?
So, is there any one thing that made me want to jump off a bridge?
不 没有什么特别的
No. Nothing unusual.
你在服用什么药物吗?
You on any medications?
用过左洛复,但是我已经不吃了
Zoloft. But I stopped.
你的医生让你停用的吗?
Yeah, did your doctor take you off the meds?
不,我自己停的
No, I just stopped on my own.
你不应该这么做
you shouldn't do that.
好了,克雷格,你看上去不像能做出什么疯狂举动
Well, Craig, it doesn't seem like you're a danger to yourself.
所以,我的建议是通知你的父母,
So, what I'm gonna suggest is that we contact your parents,
告诉他们这件事,
let them know what's going on,
然后我们会为你提供门诊服务
and then we refer you to one of our outpatient services.
我现在就需要帮助
I need help now.
我知道你很苦恼
I know you're upset.
但是,克雷格,我们接收的这些病人,
But, Craig, the people that we admit into this facility,
都病的非常非常严重
are very, very sick.
我也是
I am, too.
你能不能,随便给我点什么?
Well, can't you just, like, give me something?
要经过你家长同意才行
Not without your parents' consent.
听着,这不是个小事
Look, this is serious business.
也许我没解释清楚有多么严重
Maybe I'm not explaining right how serious this is.
这感觉就像 你要面对的事情越来越多,
It feels like everything is just building up,
而其他人,他们好像能处理好各种事情 知道吗,就是...
and everyone else, they just seem to handle everything. You know, like...
除了我,明白吗?
But not me, you know.
我很怕,好吗?
I'm scared, okay?
我不能就这么出去了
And I can't go back out there.
我不知道会...
I don't know what...
我也许会做出可怕的事情
I might do something.
我只是需要帮助,求你了 帮帮我吧
So, I just need some help. Please. I just need you to help me.
成人精神科
三楼北区
欢迎来到三楼北区,克雷格
Welcome to 3 North, Craig.
三楼北区是什么?
What exactly is 3 North?
成人精神科楼层
Our adult psychiatric floor.
噢,但是,我才16岁
Oh, but, I'm only 16.
我们的青少年楼层正在整修
Our teen floor is undergoing some renovations,
所以 所有的青少年都和成年人呆在一起
so all teens are here with the adults.
你在这儿的期间,要表现的像成人一样
And while you're with us, you'll be expected to act like one.
所以,从明天开始,
So, starting tomorrow,
你要按照日程安排行事 并且参加小组活动
you'll follow the schedule and participate in the group activities.
同时,我们会通知你的家人,让他们带来
In the meantime, we'll contact your family, and they can bring over
一些换洗的衣物,牙刷,之类的东西
a change of clothes, toothbrush, that kind of thing.
我觉得我不会在这儿呆多久
Well, I don't think I'll be here that long.
我明天还要上课,所以...
I have school tomorrow, so...
你要和密涅瓦医生讨论这件事
You'll have to discuss that with Dr. Minerva.
你带着什么尖锐的物品吗?折刀?钥匙?
Now, do you have any sharp objects on you? Pocket knife? Keys?
还有你的腰带和鞋带
And your belt and shoe laces.
我的鞋带?
My shoe laces?
我们可不能冒险
We can't take any chances.
嘿,密涅瓦医生
Hey, Dr. Minerva.
嘿,史密蒂
Hey, Smitty.
这是我们的新病号,克雷格 吉尔诺
This is our new patient, Craig Gilner.
嗨,克雷格,你好吗?
Hi, Craig. How are you?
就是,那样
Just, like, you know.
你先去看看你的房间,我们一会聊,好吗?
Well, why don't you get settled in, and we'll talk later, okay?
很高兴见到你,克雷格
Nice to meet you, Craig.
它会找到你的
It'll come to you.
早上好,吉米
Good morning, Jimmy.
那是在干什么?
What was that about?
吉米? 他患有精神分裂
Jimmy? He's a schizophrenic.
这儿有像我这种人呆的地方吗?
Is there a place here for people more like me?
我们这儿有各种各样的病人,老弟,各种各样的...
We got all kinds of patients here, man. All kinds...
嘿,嘿,鲍比!
Hey, hey, Bobby!
哥们
My man.
带我们的新朋友克雷格去转转怎么样?
How about a tour for our new friend, Craig, here? What do you say?
- 没问题,亲爱的 - 谢了,哥们
- Sure thing, babe. - Thanks, man.
我们布置你房间的时候,鲍比会带你到周围转转,行吗?
So, Bobby's gonna show you around, while we fix up your room, okay?
行
Okay.
回见
See you guys in a jiff.
这里是精神病房吗?
So, is this like a mental ward?
不是病房,是医院
Not a ward, it's a hospital.
这就是我们消遣的地方
Well, this is where we hang out.
这儿有留声机什么的
There's a record player and such.
所有的唱片都划伤了
All the records are scratched.
有些哥们喜欢来打乒乓球
Some folks like to hang out and play table tennis.
他们告诉你怎么计分了吗?
Did they tell you about the points system?
兵乓球怎么计分?
Points for ping-pong?
乒乓这名字一点不够响亮
I think the name ping-pong trivializes the sport.
言归正传,就是特殊待遇的积分,可以去娱乐室里消遣
But, I mean, like, points for privileges, to hang out in the rec room,
逛礼品店之类的
visit the gift shop, stuff like that.
想玩的话可以去玩两把
You can join them if you like.
不,免了吧
no, I'm cool.
酷克雷格 我喜欢
Cool Craig. I like that.
这是淋浴室 上面没有锁
This is the shower. It doesn't have a lock.
所以你进去的时候,把它换成"有人使用",明白?
So when you go in, put it on "in-use," get it?
- 明白了 - 你明白了,但是其他人都不明白
- I got it. - Okay, you got it, but nobody else does.
所以在你搓蛋蛋的时候他们就会闯进来
So they'll walk in on you when you're scrubbing your balls.
你可不想这样
And you don't want that.
另一个走廊也有淋浴室
There's one in the other hall, too,
但是我不会去用的 这会让所罗门很困扰
but I wouldn't use it. It bothers Solomon.
所罗门是谁?
Who's Solomon?
- 嘿,鲍比 - 嘿,卡普
- Hey, Bobby! - Hey, Cap.
这儿,这就是你跟别人联络的地方
Right here, this is where you call people.
假设你有亲朋好友的话 或者他们也会联系你
Assuming you have people. Or they can call you.
你也知道,电话
You know, telephone.
这里是电视房
And this is the TV room.
大家在里面消遣看电视
People hang out and watch TV in that room.
这也是为什么叫它电视房
That's why they call it that.
那是谁?
Who was that?
她是诺艾尔 她是青少年组的
That's Noelle. She's one of the teens.
他们告诉你青少年的大楼在整修吗?
Did they tell you about the renovations?
是的
Yeah.
你多大了?
How old are you?
十六
Sixteen.
十六!
Sixteen!
就十六岁来说 你看上去可够压抑的
You look stressed out for 16.
你需要放松自己,找个女朋友之类的
You need to relax. Get a girlfriend, or something, you know.
我正在解决呢
I'm working on it.
你在这儿究竟是做什么的?
So what is it you do here, exactly?
和你一样
Same thing as you.
你是病人?
You're a patient?
今天早晨你在急诊室里干吗?
What were you doing in the emergency room this morning?
急诊室有最好的咖啡,小子
ER has the best coffee, son.
他们就这么放你出去?
They just let you out?
不
No.
你为什么来这里?
What are you in here for?
我们去看看史密蒂弄没弄好你得房间
Let's go see if Smitty's got your room ready.
嘿,穆塔达,你有了个新室友,老兄
Hey, Muqtada, got a new roommate, man.
嘿
Hey.
别往心里去,老弟 他就这么孤僻
Don't take it personal, man. He doesn't really talk much.
我根本没看到 他出过这个房间
And I've actually never seen him leave the room.
好了,大伙,五分钟后吃饭
Okay, guys, lunch in five.
午餐都吃什么?
What do they have for lunch?
什么?
I'm sorry?
拜托,把灯关了
Please, turn out light.
密涅瓦医生
Dr. Minerva.
我现在感觉好多了
I'm feeling much better now.
今天早上我有点不舒服,但是现在没事了
I was feeling bad this morning, but I'm okay now.
所以,如果可以的话,我就回家了
So, you know, I'd like to go home, if that's cool.
上面写着你有自杀倾向 而且是主动要求进来的
It says here you're suicidal and asked to be admitted.
是啊,我原以为你们能做出什么快速治疗
Yeah, I thought you guys could do something quick.
像给我些镇定药让我安定下来
You know, like give me some medication to make me feel better.
或者...
Or...
听着,我不觉得我有什么大问题
Look, I didn't think that I'd be committed.
我真的不属于这里
I really don't think I belong here.
很多病人一开始都这么觉得 时间长了就好了
A lot of patients feel that way at first. Just give it a little time.
多长?
How little?
五天
Five days.
五天?
Five days?
不会超过三十天 我们会对你进行诊断
No more than 30. We'll have an evaluation
看看你能否在周四出院
to see if you're ready to leave on Thursday.
我不能等到周四
I can't be here until Thursday
因为我会旷课,我朋友可能会发现我在这里
because I'll miss school, and my friends might find out where I am.
这没什么可感到羞耻的,克雷格
It's nothing to be ashamed of, Craig.
抑郁是一种医学疾病
Depression is a medical illness.
如果你有糖尿病,你会因此感到不好意思吗?
If you were diabetic, would you be embarrassed by that?
那至少能不能让我和我妈聊几句...
Well, can I at least talk to my mom about this before...
当然可以,克雷格,我刚刚和她通过话,她很想见你
Of course, Craig. I just spoke to her, she's very anxious to see you.
克雷格!
Craig!
不要为我现在的处境而怪我父母
Don't blame my parents for how messed up I am.
我爸工作太忙
Okay, so my dad works too much.
我妈又有点脆弱
And my mom's a little too fragile.
而我小妹貌似是什么天才儿童
And my sister's some kind of child genius.
但并不是说我从没得到什么关爱
But it's not like I was never hugged as a child or anything.
实际上,他们给予了我非常多的鼓励
In fact, they've been pretty supportive through all this.
我知道你压力很大,但我根本没想到
I knew you were having a hard time, but I had no idea.
你是...这真是...
That you were... That it was...
你太勇敢了,亲爱的 我真为你骄傲
Well, you're so brave, honey. I'm so proud of you.
真的吗?
Really?
因为我现在还犹豫不定呢
'Cause I was actually having second thoughts.
噢,不,亲爱的 医生们需要你
Oh, no, hon. I think the doctors said they need you
呆在这里几天以便观察
to stay here for a couple of days for observation.
我觉得这对你有好处
I think that's a real good idea.
但你可能不知道
But I don't think you really understand, okay?
这儿的一些人都病的非常严重
Some of the people in here are really messed up.
我室友一周没离开房间了
I don't think my roommate's left the room in weeks.
我想我们还是
I think we better leave it up
让医生做决定吧
to the doctor's discretion, you know.
我们都努力了...
We've tried and...
他们都是专家,都能以专业的方式帮助你
They're professionals, they can help you in ways that we can't.
而且我觉得...
And I think it's...
这地方真不错,是吧,乔治?
I think it looks like a real nice place. Right, George?
别碰我的口袋!
Take your hands out of my pockets!
是啊,我真想加入这里
Yeah. When can I join?
我也是 我也能呆在这里吗?
Me, too. Can I stay, too?
噢,不行,亲爱的,我们会再来探望的
Oh, no, honey. But we'll come and visit.
他们拿走了我的手机,所以可能会有人往家里打电话
They took my cell phone, so some people might try to call the house.
拜托不要告诉他们我在这里
Just please do not tell them that I'm in here.
这是一些衣物,洗漱用品之类的东西
Here are some clothes, and toiletries and stuff.
多吃点东西,好吗?
And will you eat something, please?
- 伊恩 柯蒂斯 - 谁?
- Ian Curtis. - Who?
快乐小分队的成员 上吊自杀了
Dude from Joy Division. Hung himself.
科特 科本
Kurt Cobain.
弗洛伊德
Freud.
欧内斯特 海明威
Ernest Hemingway.
萨尔瓦多 阿兰达
Salvador Allende.
上帝啊,姑娘们,能说些我们认识的人吗?
Jesus Christ, girl. Can you pick somebody we've heard of for once?
智利总统
Chilean president.
宁愿自杀也不向法西斯军事政变投降
Shot himself rather than surrender to a fascist military coup.
这应该不算是吧
I don't think that counts.
当然算数了
Of course, it counts.
如果他横竖都是死,那就不算数
If he was going to die anyway, it doesn't count.
嘿,克雷格!
Hey, Craig!
来和爷们们呆在一起
Come sit with the men.
克雷格,这是我兄弟,强尼,还有这个二货,亨布尔
Craig, this is my pal, Johnny, and this clown right here, this is Humble.
有女朋友吗?
You got a girlfriend?
他正在解决呢
He's working on it.
那有几个很合适你的小姑娘哦
They got some cute ones your age.
我曾经有过很多女人,小子
I had a lot of women in my day, kid.
是吗?
Yeah?
你不用非得显得这么吃惊
You don't have to act so surprised.
当年牛逼的时候,我就是品鲍爵士
Back in the day, I was Sir Lick-a-Lot.
不信问鲍比
Ask Bobby.
你想知道泡妞的必杀诀窍吗?
You want to know the secret to keeping any woman under your spell?
我爱你
I love you.
就这样?
That's it?
就这样 但是你会弹吉他 也无伤大雅
That's it. But it don't hurt if you can play guitar.
别给他灌输这些歪理邪说,
Don't mess with the kid's mind,
他已经够操蛋的了
he's already screwed up enough as it is.
你为什么这么操蛋,小子
Why are you so screwed, kid?
别管闲事,亨布尔
Mind your own business, Humble.
好吧
That's cool.
但是你要知道,克雷格,如果你不敞开心扉,你永远不会痊愈
But you should know, Craig, if you don't open up, you're never going to heal.
嘿,攒了多少钱了?
Hey, what's the pot up to now?
- 十一 - 十一?
- Eleven. - Eleven?
昨天还是十二的
Yesterday, it was 12.
亨布尔吃了一美元
Humble ate a buck.
亨布尔吃了一美元?
Humble ate a buck?
主任医师跟他赌一美元,他不会吃下去 他赢了
The professor bet him a dollar, he wouldn't eat it. He won.
这是个什么世界啊?
What is the world coming to?
我告诉你,这儿有大把不务正业的人
Bunch of nut jobs in here, I'll tell you that.
钱是干吗的?
What's the money for?
披萨派对
Pizza party.
我们就不必吃这些垃圾了
So we don't have to eat this crap.
他们同意了,但是要自己拿钱
They say we can have one, but we gotta pay for it ourselves.
我有八美元
Well, I have eight dollars.
你没必要这么显摆,克雷格
Well, you don't have to go bragging about it, Craig.
这儿的人都是一无所有
People in here have nothing.
给他们点面子,好吗
Show a little humility, please.
不...我不是想...
No. I didn't mean... It's...
没关系 你还年轻 有时间来学习
It's okay. You're young, you'll learn.
克雷格 吃饭给你增加了两个积分,老弟
Craig. You get two points for eating, man.
我打赌史密蒂身上有15美元
I bet Smitty's got 15 bucks on him.
他还有20美元,我看见了
And he's got a 20 spot. I saw it.
我们去停车场偷袭他
Let's go jump him in the parking lot.
钱藏在帽子底下
It's under the hat.
钱藏在帽子底下?
It's under the hat?
抱歉
Sorry.
明白
Check.
克雷格,在三楼北区还适应吗?
So, Craig, how are you adjusting to 3 North?
还行吧
Okay, I guess.
穆罕默德医生写道 你一直服用左洛复
Dr. Mahmoud wrote that you were taking Zoloft,
但是三周前停用了,是吗?
but went off it three weeks ago. Is that right?
是的
Yeah.
你在看精神科医生吗?
Do you see a therapist?
耶纳夫医生让我服用左洛复的
Dr. Yanof was the one who prescribed me the Zoloft.
我基本上每月都接受她的治疗
I see her every, you know, month or so.
为什么停止服用了?
Why did you stop taking it?
可能是觉得自己好多了 不再需要服用了
I guess I thought I was better. Like I didn't need it.
也许这正是药起了作用
Maybe that's because it was working.
你能向我描述一下你来之前的感觉吗?
Can you describe to me how you were feeling before coming here this morning?
压抑
I guess, depressed.
焦虑,紧张
Anxious, stressed.
你觉得最近的压力比平常要大吗?
Have you been feeling more stress than usual lately?
有什么特殊原因吗?
Any reason in particular?
有一所富兰克林盖茨暑期学校
Yeah. There's this Franklin Gates Summer Semester thing
是我爸...
that my dad...
嗯,是我很想去的
Well, that I really want to get into.
但是申请截止时间只有一周了
But the application is due in a week
而我甚至都没有仔细考虑这件事
and I haven't even looked at it.
为什么没有?
Why not?
每次我一想到它,
Every time I think about it,
我的大脑就产生了录取不了的想法
my brain starts this cycling thing about not getting in.
如果你没被录取上会发生什么?
What would happen if you didn't get in?
那我就不能把它填到我的大学申请上了
Then I wouldn't be able to put it on my college applications.
也就是说我上不了好大学了
Which means I wouldn't get into a good college.
但是连亚当斯密都预知不了现代资本主义的不公平待遇
But not even Adam Smith could have foreseen the inequities of modern capitalism.
如果我上不了好大学,就找不到好工作
If I didn't get into a good college, I wouldn't have a good job.
通过单边主义控制伊朗的局势
Diffusing the situation in Iran through unilateral diplomacy
是我作为总司令的首要目标
is my top priority as Commander in Chief.
也就是说我过不了上流生活
Which means I wouldn't be able to afford a good lifestyle.
嘿,MTV 我是你们的偶像 克雷格 吉尔诺
Hey, MTV. It's your boy, Craig Gilner.
欢迎来到我的小窝
Welcome to my crib.
我就找不到女朋友
So I wouldn't be able to find a girlfriend.
也就是说我可能换上抑郁症
Which means I'd probably get depressed.
然后像穆塔达一样在这里度过自己的余生
And I'd end up like Muqtada in a place like this for the rest of my life.
所以,如果我没被录取会发生什么?
So, what would happen if I didn't get in?
我不知道 一言难尽
I don't know. It's hard to explain.
你有可以倾诉的对象吗?朋友?家人?
Do you have anyone you can explain it to? Friends? Family?
我有朋友和家人,但有时候你很难向他们说清楚
I have friends and family, but it's not always easy.
有个支持你的人是很重要的
It's important to have a support system.
一个你能为之倾诉的人
People you can really talk to.
还有什么其他的病状吗?
Have you been having any other symptoms?
我的饮食有点问题  我控制不了
I have trouble eating. I can't keep it down.
好吧
All right.
你从明天开始参加小组活动
You'll start group activities tomorrow,
我们周二再进行复查
we'll check in again on Tuesday.
有什么问题吗?
You have any questions?
有
Yes.
如果我感觉好多了,我明天能离开这里吗?
If I'm feeling better, do you think I can get out of here by tomorrow?
因为我还要上学而且这些申请和...
Because I have school and this application and...
五天,克雷格 最少五天
Five days, Craig. Minimum.
我知道这里一开始看起来很奇怪
I know this seems like a strange place at first,
但是你要尽量适应
but try to make the most of it.
周一
今天是周一
It's Monday.
我不应该在一个抑郁的埃及中年大叔旁边醒来
I shouldn't be waking up next to some depressive middle-aged Egyptian dude.
我不应该在一个男女混住楼层的没有锁的淋浴室里洗澡
I shouldn't be showering on a co-ed floor in a stall without a lock.
我不应该在一堆精神分裂患者和病态者后面排队等着吃药
I shouldn't be lining up for meds behind schizophrenics and sociopaths.
这可是周一,我应该在学校上课
It's Monday, I should be in school.
但我猜那(学校压力)也是导致我来这里的原因
But I guess that's what got me here in the first place.
我父母上学的时候,
When my parents went to school,
他们会去离家最近的一所学校
they just went to the one closest to their house.
很有道理,是吧?
Makes sense, right?
现在很多地方还是这样
A lot of places are still like this.
克里夫兰,或许丹佛
Cleveland, probably Denver.
但不是纽约
But not New York.
这里有适合科学天才的学校,比如...
You've got schools for science geeks like...
布朗克斯科技高中
Bronx High School of Science.
培养戏剧演员的学校
Schools for thespians.
拉瓜迪亚高中 表演艺术的殿堂
The LaGuardia School for the Performing Arts.
适合改良派的学校
Schools for do-gooders.
埃尔蓬特学院 为了正义与和平!
El Puente Academy for Peace and Justice.
但是纽约所有公立学校中最具竞争力的是这一所
But the most competitive of all New York City public schools is this one.
预科先修学校
Executive Pre-Professional.
我的学校
My school.
这个亿万富翁慈善家叫做热拉尔卢茨
This billionaire philanthropist named Gerard Lutz
以公立学校的制度建立了这所学校
set it up in conjunction with the public school system.
所以这不是什么上东区精英去的私立学校
So it's not some private school for elite Upper-East-Siders.
不管你是靠政府救济生活的,
You can be on welfare and food stamps,
还是你父母拥有一座南太平洋的小岛
or your parents can own an island in the South Pacific.
这都无关紧要
It doesn't matter.
只要你是全纽约前800名最聪明
You'll be accepted as long as you're one of the 800
最多才的学生,他们就会接收你
smartest and most accomplished students in the five boroughs.
像这些学生
Like these kids here.
萨哈拉 帕特尔
学术能力评估考试:2380[2400] 研究生入学考试:1530[1600] (写作5.5)[6分]
法学院入学考试:174[180] 医学院入学考试:42[45] (写作S)[最低为J，最高为T]
[]里的分数为满分
詹姆斯 霍华德
三次超级挑战赛冠军(2007,2009,2010)
美著名编程大赛
埃伦 费兹卡诺德
戴维森青年哲学奖获得者(2008,2009)
全美辩论大赛冠军(演讲与辩论)
美国偶像区域半决赛选手(第八季)
克雷格 吉尔诺
这肯定是个严重的错误,因为不知为何...
There must have been a serious clerical error, because somehow...
我被录取了
I got in.
- 我也是 - 我也是
- Me, too. - Me, too.
- 你也是? - 你也是?
- You, too? - You, too?
这是我最好的朋友,埃伦,第一次挨尼娅的调情拳
That's my best friend, Aaron, getting flirt-punched by Nia for the first time.
之后发生了很多次
There were many more of those.
接下来就是手拉手,亲吻,最终就是,做爱
Followed by hand-holding, kissing and eventually, sex.
我不想幻想这个场景
I don't like to picture that one.
我好想挨一次尼娅的调情拳
What I would give to be flirt-punched by Nia just once.
这就开始了...
And so it began...
看看这些宝贝
Look at those mahatmas.
我一直想要一辆哈雷和美女,拉风的宝贝
I always wanted a Harley with hot, tight mahatmas.
哈雷就给你了,美女给我享用
You can have the mahatmas, I just want the beaver.
嘿,鲍比,快看这车
Hey, Bobby, check out this bike.
我才不看这种得不到的东西
Yeah, I don't get wrapped in a bunch of stuff I can't have.
放松点,玩的个事,老兄
Relax, it's just for fun, bro.
一点都不好玩
That's not fun.
这是广告,哥们
That's propaganda, man.
所有这些大肆鼓吹的东西
All those Madison Avenue types.
告诉你应该怎样享受生活
Telling you how to live your life.
香车 辣女
Fast cars, hot chicks,
美食 靓衣
Reese's Pieces, Gucci.
奶油太妃糖
Werther's Original.
我才不信这些鬼话
I don't buy into that bullshit.
你要吃你的卷饼吗,克雷格?
Are you gonna eat your burrito, Craig?
我不饿,你吃吧
No, I'm not hungry. You can have it.
你好,早餐卷饼先生
Hello, Mr. Breakfast Burrito.
亨布尔,放回去
Humble, put that back.
他说我可以吃的
He said I could have it.
是的,没关系
Yeah, it's really fine.
克雷格也要吃的,放回去
Craig's gotta eat, too. Put it back.
不关你事,鲍比
Take a hike, Bob.
他不饿
He's not hungry.
谢了,鲍比,我真不饿
Thanks, Bobby, but I'm really not hungry.
行,我管你吃不吃的
Fine, what do I care if you eat?
我听说今天早上发生了一些小摩擦
I understand there was an incident this morning.
有人想说说吗?
Would anyone care to talk about it?
有关早餐卷饼的事
Something involving a breakfast burrito.
强尼?
Johnny?
是鲍比和亨布尔之间的过节,问他们
It was between Bobby and Humble. Ask them.
我想听听旁观者的看法
I was interested in hearing it from an impartial observer.
让我说的话,我认为是鲍比的面谈
Well, if you want my opinion, I think Bobby has been on edge
让他局促不安,他这么是烦躁是因为他很紧张
because of his interview, and he's lashing out because he's nervous.
评论的很不错,强尼
Interesting observation, Johnny.
我的痔疮也复发了,强尼
My hemorrhoids are flaring up too, Johnny.
你想跟大家谈谈这个吗?
Want to tell the group about that?
痔疮!它会来到你身边!
Hemorrhoids! It'll come to ya!
鲍比,如果不想说出你的感受也没事
Bobby, it's okay if you want to keep your feelings private,
但是你应该知道 对明天的面谈感到紧张
but you should know that there's nothing wrong with being nervous
没什么大不了的
about your interview tomorrow.
我不是对面谈感到紧张
I'm not nervous about my interview.
那是什么原因,鲍比?
Then what is it, Bob?
也许他饿了
Maybe he's hungry.
他看上去不像是饿了
He doesn't look hungry.
他看上去很疲惫
He looks tired.
你昨晚睡觉了吗?
Did you sleep last night?
他今天没吃饭
He didn't eat today.
他吃了
Yes, he did.
你看到他吃饭了吗?
Did you see him eat?
我敢肯定他吃了
I'm pretty sure he ate.
我没看到他吃饭
I didn't see him eat.
我一疲惫就感到焦虑
I get anxious when I'm tired.
好了,听着
Okay, listen.
我不饿而且我也不累  是因为这件毛衣
I'm not hungry and I'm not tired. It's just the sweater.
这是我明天面谈唯一能穿的衣服
It's all I have for my interview tomorrow.
我说了是因为面谈
I told you it was the interview.
这毛衣很不错,鲍比
It's a nice sweater, Bob.
不,才不呢 它闻起来像一个流浪汉身上的创可贴
No, it's not. It smells like a hobo's Band-Aid.
但是它很衬你啊
But it looks good on you.
就像你的头发衬你一样
About as good as your hair looks on you.
鲍比,别挖苦别人,拜托
Bobby, no insults, please.
我能借你件衬衣
I can loan you a shirt.
怎么借,克雷格?
What was that, Craig?
我给我妈打个电话 让她捎来一件我爸的衬衣就行
I'll just call my mom and have her bring one of my dad's shirts over.
一点不麻烦 我就住在离这儿的两个街区
It's not a problem. I live like two blocks away.
不用了,谢谢
No, thanks.
鲍比!收下吧
Bobby! Take the shirt.
是啊,他想要帮你,鲍比
Yeah, he's trying to help, Bob.
这是个不错的提议,克雷格
It's a very nice offer, Craig.
鲍比,你为什么不愿接受呢?
Bobby, why are you reluctant to accept it?
因为我不想要别人的施舍
'Cause I don't want any handouts.
这并不是施舍
It wouldn't exactly be a handout.
他只是借给你
He'd just be loaning it to you.
好吧,我要了 只要你别再烦我了就成
Okay, I'll take it. As long as you'll get off my back.
你到底想不想要,鲍比?
Do you want the shirt, Bobby?
我...
I would...
我想要
I would like the shirt.
克雷格?
Craig?
衣服腋下有点发黄不介意吧?
Is it okay if it has yellow armpit stains?
抱歉,很愚蠢的玩笑
Sorry, it was a dumb joke.
你什么时候能让我再见到她?
When are you going to let me get to see her again?
因为我是她爸爸 你以为我没有...
Because I'm her father. You don't think that I have...
这算什么?我有... 我会有地方住的
What's that? I do have... I will have a place.
周四我就能找到地方住 真的
I have a... I'm gonna have a place on Thursday. It's true.
听着,我没求过你什么
Listen, I never asked you for anything.
你能不能,就这么一次,照我说的做 喂?喂!
Could you just, for once, maybe do what I say. Hello? Hello!
你之前表现的非常绅士 今晚七点 电视房外的长椅边见 - 诺艾尔
你有两条新留言
You have two new messages.
嘿,克雷格 是我
Hey, Craig. It's me.
好吧,其实, 她现在可能不在浴缸里面,
Okay. So, she's probably not in the bathtub right now,
但有时我就喜欢像这样幻想尼娅
but this is how I sometimes like to picture Nia.
很病态,我知道
It's sick, I know.
你之前表现的有些奇怪,
You were acting a little weird earlier,
所以我只想确保一切都好
so I just wanted to make sure everything's okay.
好了,就是这样
All right, that's it.
我和埃伦在一起 他太容易被人利用了 拜!
I'm with Aaron. He's being such a tool. Bye!
你好,吉尔诺先生 我是你的理科老师,雷诺兹
Hello, Mr. Gilner, this is your science teacher, Mr. Reynolds.
我们需要好好谈谈你缺席的实验作业
We really need to talk about your missing lab assignments.
一共五个
Five of them.
喂?
Hello?
嘿,尼娅 好吗?
Hey, Nia. What's up?
嘿! 我刚完成了暑期学校的申请 如果没被录取我会疯的
Hey! Just finishing my Gates Summer app. I'll freak if I don't get in.
你怎么了?
What's up with you?
就是有点...
Just feeling kind of, you know...
啊,我注意到了 这就是你今天为什么没来学校?
Yeah, I noticed. Is that why you weren't in school today?
是啊,我有点不舒服,所以就呆在家里了
Yeah, I was feeling pretty shitty, so I just stayed home.
嗯 我有时也会这样
Yeah. I get like that sometimes, too.
抑郁之类的
Depressed or whatever.
你采取过什么治疗措施吗?
Do you take anything for it?
听着,我从没告诉过别人
Look, I never told anybody this.
连埃伦也没有,但是,如果能让你感到好受些的话...
Not even Aaron, but, if it makes you feel any better,
我在看精神科医生
I see a therapist.
真的?
Really?
已经一年多了
For, like, over a year now.
我一点都不知道
I had no idea.
让人很难为情
Yeah, it's pretty embarrassing.
- 我服用左洛复 - 不是吧!
- I take Zoloft. - Shut up!
真的
I do.
噢,天呐! 我们真的很惨
Oh, my God! We're like so screwed up.
是啊,我们就像病友一样
Yeah, we're like partners in mental illness.
病的最惨的那种
The illest.
我是所罗门 能不能请你小声点
I'm Solomon. I would ask you to please keep it down.
我要休息
I'm trying to rest.
克雷格,那是谁?
Craig, who is that?
打扰下
Excuse me.
- 没事吧? - 你还要打多久?
- Is everything okay? - Will you be much longer?
一会就好
One second, please.
你在玩网游吗?
Are you like in a crack den or something?
啊,不,没什么 一切都...
Yeah, no, it's fine. Everything's...
它会找上你的 它总是会找上你的
It'll come to you. It will always come to you.
你在哪儿啊?
Where are you?
我要挂了,尼娅 拜
I gotta go, Nia. Bye.
克雷格
Craig...
你用吧
It's all yours.
谢谢你,妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
知道吗,你爸今天很想来的,
You know, your dad really wanted to be here today,
但是他遇到了客户危机
he just had a client crisis.
客户危机?
Client crisis?
是啊,但是他说,他明天肯定会来的
Yeah, but he said, he's for sure coming tomorrow.
交到朋友了吗?
Have you made any friends yet?
我想有吧
Yeah, I guess.
你和那个变性人交了朋友吗?
Are you friends with the tranny?
哦,那个变性人
Oh, the tranny.
不算是
Not really.
跟学校联系过了吗?
Did you talk to my school?
因为我不能让他们发现我在这种地方
Because I really can't have them finding I'm in a place like this.
这会毁了我的未来
It could really damage my future.
没有,没有 我只是说你进了医院
No, no. I just said you were in the hospital.
没再具体说什么
I didn't say anything specific.
很好 我最不希望发生的就是让他们知道我在这里
Good. The last thing I need is for them to find out I've been institutionalized.
人妖!
Transvestite!
神经病!
Schizo!
你干什么呢,亲爱的?
What's going on, babe?
抱歉,我是来送衬衣的
Sorry. I was just dropping the shirt off.
她很漂亮,是吧?
She's cute, isn't she?
是啊 你的孩子?
Yeah. Is she yours?
维罗妮卡  就像埃尔维斯 科斯特洛唱的那样
Veronica. Like the Elvis Costello song.
她多大了?
How old is she?
八又四分之三岁
Eight and three-quarters.
这是她自己说的 四分之三
That's what she says. Three quarters.
祝你面谈顺利
Well, good luck with your interview.
是为了什么,如果不介意我问的话?
What's it for, if you don't mind me asking?
进入集体式家庭
A group home.
简单的说,在他们周四让我卷铺盖走的时候 我需要个住的地方
Basically, I need a place to live when they kick me out of here on Thursday.
如果你想找个人练习的话请告诉我
Let me know if you need somebody to practice with or something.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
面谈前的模拟练习 这样你能准备的更充足
Like a practice interview. So you're better prepared.
是吗?
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
想试试吗?
You want to try?
现在?
You want to try now?
如果你没事的话
If you're not doing anything.
好,稍等
Okay, great. Hold on.
让我穿上正式的衣服再开始
Let me do this with the official shirt on.
准备好了?
Okay. You're ready?
稍等一会 我不知道这样...
Hold on one second. I don't know if I'll do it like...
那一种造型更好,比如...
Which is better, like...
这种?
This?
嗯 看起来很自然
Yeah. That looks natural.
好
Okay.
放松点
You can relax.
我很紧张
I'm nervous.
你为什么觉得自己有资格住进群体式家庭?
Okay, why is it that you think you qualify to live in this group home?
因为如果你拒绝了,我就无家可归了
Because if you don't accept me, I'll be homeless.
好吧,挺好
Okay, good.
我觉得你可以了
Yeah, I think you're ready.
是吗? 语气听上去不会太绝望?
Really? I didn't sound too desperate?
不会,但是...
No. But, uh...
你最好表现出一些 在这儿学到的积极的东西
You might want to focus on the positive things that you get from this experience
而不是...
as opposed to, you know...
消极的
The negative.
没错 比如你能把什么带回家
Exactly. Like what is it that you could bring to the home?
一些只有你能提供的特殊的东西
Something special that only you could offer.
什么都可以 比如你有了一个更好的心态?
It could be anything. Maybe you have a great attitude?
没有
No.
你能很好的照顾自己?
You always clean up after yourself?
不太行
Not really.
我认为这种情况下你可以不用这么诚实
You know, I think in these situations it's okay to bend the truth just a little bit.
我只是不想让别人对我期望太高 然后让他们失望
I just don't want to get people's expectations up and then disappoint them later.
就是这样 你很实事求是 你就告诉他们这个
That's it. You're pragmatic. That's what you tell them.
很不错,是吧?
Okay, yeah. Right?
是的,你一定会表现出色
Yeah, I know you're gonna do great.
谢谢
Thanks.
想打乒乓球吗?
You want to play some table tennis?
我打的很烂
I'm pretty terrible at table tennis.
没事 就是玩玩 来吧
It's all right. It's just for fun. Come on.
我们经常在这里玩 但问题是,
We play a lot around here. The problem is,
很多人吃药吃多了 你无法与他进行比赛
most people are too zonked out on their meds to compete.
一比零
One, zip.
她骗人的
She's a liar.
求你了,宝贝,宝贝 听着 听着
Please, baby. Baby. Please listen. Listen.
我爱你
I love you.
别管他了
Don't worry about it.
我当然原谅你了,宝贝
Of course, I forgive you, baby.
强尼可不在电话上亲吻
Johnny doesn't phone kiss.
你来了
You came.
我还有别的计划,但是我给取消了
Yeah. I mean, I had other plans, but I canceled them.
很好 我还以为我昨天会把你吓跑呢
Good. I thought I might have scared you off yesterday.
噢,名人自杀
Oh, yeah, celebrity suicide.
很怪异
It's kind of weird.
听着,我们今天换种游戏玩
Okay, so check it out. We're gonna play a different game today.
好
Okay.
我问你个问题 然后你再问我个问题
I ask you a question and you ask me a question.
要回答吗?
Do we answer them?
随你便,但是不管怎样,
It's up to you, but no matter what,
你要以问题作为结束
you have to finish with a question.
- 开始了 准备好了吗? - 是的
- Here we go. You ready? - Yeah.
我说了要以问题作为结束
I said finish with a question.
你很蠢吗?
Are you stupid?
不...你呢?
Uh, no... Are you?
就是这样 你觉得我看上去很糟吗?
There you go. Do you think I'm gross looking?
不 你看上去好极了
No. You look awesome.
你的问题?
What's your question?
你为什么约我到这儿?
Why'd you invite me here?
我觉得你借给鲍比衬衣非常好心
I thought it was nice that you loaned Bobby your shirt.
你不觉得这是一个了解别人的好方法吗?
Don't you think this is a good way to get to know someone?
当然
Sure.
你以前玩过这游戏吗?
Have you played this before?
在这里没有
Not in here.
你是处男吗?
Are you a virgin?
那么...
So...
你在这儿呆了多久了?
How long have you been here?
很会转移话题,克雷格
Nice transition, Craig.
二十一天 谁把你带来的?
Twenty-one days. Who dragged you here?
我自己来的
I checked myself in, I guess.
有点算是,命运使然吧
Kind of, by accident.
自杀者帮助热线让我来的
The suicide hotline said to come.
你为什么在这儿呆了这么久?
Why are you here so long?
他们觉得我可能还会再次伤害自己
They think I might cut myself again.
你为什么会打自杀者帮助热线?
Why'd you call the suicide hotline?
我猜...
I guess...
可能 我并不是真想自杀
Maybe I didn't really want to kill myself.
但是我却这样做了
But I kind of did.
这有道理吗?
Does that make sense?
你在哪里上学?
So, where do you go?
预科先修学校 你呢?
Executive Pre-Professional. You?
德芬
Delfin.
你们不强制要求穿校服的,是吧?
You're not some sort of school uniform perv, are you?
你们还穿校服?
You guys wear uniforms?
我就知道
I knew it.
抱歉,我要占用一下你的私人空间
Okay, sorry, I'm gonna invade your personal space for one second.
为什么?
Why?
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
- 你吓了我一跳 - 许个愿
- You shocked me. - Make a wish.
我们现在干什么?
What do we do now?
你还在玩那个游戏吗?
Are you still playing?
没 你呢?
No. Are you?
看看谁先跑到艺术室
I'll race you to arts and crafts.
嘿 你们 别跑 拜托
Hey, guys. No running, please.
哎吆,哎吆,哎吆!
Well, well, well!
还在解决那事呢,酷克雷格?
Still working on it, Cool Craig?
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
你们两个刚才在外面玩问题游戏呢  这就是我想的
I think the two of you were playing the question game outside. That's what I think.
事实就是你想的那样
Well, I guess it is what you think then.
我猜也是
I thought so.
这里提供免费艺术娱乐疗法,你们这些迟到的人
This is free period arts recreational therapy for you latecomers.
我是乔安妮 娱乐主管
I'm Joanie, recreation director.
我是克雷格
I'm Craig.
材料都在桌子上,克雷格 开始画吧
Well, materials are on the table, Craig. So just go for it.
不了 我不太会画画
That's okay. I don't really draw.
你肯定会的 不一定非得是有意义的,
Sure you do. It doesn't have to be representative,
也可以是抽象的,想画什么都行
it can be abstract, whatever you want.
我就想随便玩玩,如果可以的话
Well, I'll just hang out, if that's okay.
大家 我们的新成员 克雷格
Everybody? Our new guest, Craig,
碰到了创作灵感的枯竭
is having what we call an artistic block.
他不知道要画什么
He doesn't know what to draw.
海狸(也有女性生殖器的意思)怎么样?
How about beavers?
亨布尔,我们不能画你说的那种海狸
Humble, we do not draw the sort of beavers you're talking about.
是吗?
Oh, really?
这画的还真不错
That's actually nice.
我还以为会画成鲍鱼呢  画的不错
I thought it was gonna be a vagina. That's nice.
擀面杖!
Rolling pin!
什么,罗杰? 你说什么?
What was that, Roger? Did you say something?
这太囧了
This is weird.
听着,如果你不画些什么 她会一直骚扰你
Look, she's not gonna get off your back until you draw something.
什么都行
Can be anything.
我打赌你那一团糟的脑子里肯定有一些疯狂的念头
I bet you got some crazy stuff in that messed up little mind of yours.
美国已经实现了历史上为时最长的和平时期经济扩张
America has created the longest peace time economic expansion in our history.
布鲁克林 1999年
妈的!
Shit!
有着大约1千8百万个新岗位,
With nearly 18 million new jobs,
工资上涨幅度是通货膨胀率的两倍以上
wages rising at more than twice the rate of inflation.
历史上最高的住宅自有率
The highest home ownership in history.
克雷格,亲爱的,怎么了?
Craig, honey, what's the matter?
我做不到 五岁我就已经是个失败者了
I can't do it. Five years old and I'm already a failure.
你做不到什么?
What can't you do?
我都不能在描图纸上画出曼哈顿
I can't even trace Manhattan on tracing paper.
描图纸啊! 开什么玩笑?
Tracing paper! Are you kidding me?
克雷格,你不能画完之后要求它是多么的完美
Craig, you can't trace freehand and expect it to be perfect.
为什么不能?
Why not?
因为,亲爱的,你才五岁
Because, honey, you're five years old.
这不是借口
That's no excuse.
莫扎特五岁的时候就创作了三曲大型交响乐
Mozart composed three major symphonies by the time he was five.
实际上,克雷格,是四岁
Actually, Craig, it was four.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
与其描画出曼哈顿的地图
Instead of trying to trace maps of Manhattan,
为什么不自己创作一幅呢?
why don't you just make up your own maps?
一片虚构的地域
Of imaginary places.
看来某人灵感迸发了
Oh, looks like somebody got unblocked.
真是太不可思议了
That is extraordinary.
- 画的什么? - 很漂亮
- What is it? - It's so pretty.
像大脑之类的东西,是吗?
Looks like a brain or something, right?
没错,是一幅大脑地图
Yeah, it's a brain map.
画的真不错
It's a great brain map.
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
真是个人才
A smart talent.
很高兴认识你,克雷格 周三再见 同一时间同一地点
- 我没看出来像大脑 - 像一座城市
- I didn't get the brain part. - Looks like a city.
嘿,克雷格,有人打电话找你
Hey, Craig, you got a phone call, man.
喂?
Hello?
是精神病院吗?
Is this the loony bin?
好吧,我现在把画面给暂停了,
Okay, I've been putting this off,
因为你应该多了解一下我的死党,埃伦
but I guess you should know more about my best friend, Aaron.
他就是那种什么都玩得转的人
He's the kind of guy that life just comes easy to.
他平均分有4.6分 这简直就是不可思议
He's got a 4.6 GPA. I don't even see how that's possible.
他可能会被盖茨暑期班录取,
And he'll probably get into the Gates Summer Program,
然后对外宣称...
and claim something like...
我根本就没申请那里 是他们找上我的
I didn't even apply to that thing. They totally recruited me.
无所谓了,写在我的大学申请表上能漂亮些
Whatever, it'll look good on my college apps.
并不是他非需要不可 他课外活动的表现简直就是超人
Not that he'd need it. His extra-curriculars are out of control.
我是说,他无所不能
I mean, Aaron does everything.
他玩体育
He plays sports.
他创建了电影俱乐部
He started a film society.
他自己做了一个适配器 能把留声机唱片转化为MP3
He invented that adapter thing that converts vinyl albums into MP3s.
我根本无法与之相比
I just couldn't compete.
你怎么知道这个号码的?
How'd you get this number?
我女朋友给我的
My girl gave it to me.
你怎么跑到成人精神治疗室了?
How'd you end up in adult psych?
那里提供啤酒吗?
Do they serve beer in there?
哥们,能给我带些维柯丁吗?
Dude, can you get me any Vicodin?
拜托了 你们 别玩他了
Come on, guys. Leave him alone.
说实在的,克雷格,到底怎么了?
Seriously, Craig, what happened?
我也不知道 晚上过的很不好
I don't know. I had a bad night.
什么意思,晚上过的不好?
What do you mean, a bad night?
就是感觉...
I'm just feeling...
哥们,你只是需要放松,知道吗?
Dude, you just need to chill more, okay?
你的问题就是,你从来不知道放松
Your problem is, you never chill.
我今晚要放松一下,你去哪?
I'm gonna be chilling tonight, where you gonna be?
这儿 我就呆在这儿
Here. I'm gonna be here.
噢,天呐,克雷格! 你根本就没问题
Oh, my God, Craig! There is so nothing wrong with you.
我有 我有抑郁症
Yes, there is. I'm depressed.
我还因此吃药呢 问尼娅
I take pills for it. Ask Nia.
问尼娅什么?
Ask Nia what?
克雷格!
Craig!
算了 如果你不是这副鸟德行
Forget it. Maybe if you weren't such a dick,
别人会愿意告诉你,让你了解这些事情
people would talk to you more and you would know this kind of stuff.
哥们,你是要博取我女朋友的同情吗?
Dude, is this some kind of pity play for my girlfriend?
- 埃伦... - 什么?
- Aaron... - What?
操你妈
Fuck you.
我知道,小声点,抱歉
I know, keep it down. I'm sorry.
我一个朋友都没有
I don't have any friends.
交朋友是门学问
This is very tough thing to learn.
看起来有人忘了要交盖茨暑期学校的申请
Seems here someone neglected to turn in their Gates Summer application.
是谁不想 这个暑假到富兰克林盖茨学校学习的?
Who is it that doesn't want to study at Franklin Gates this summer?
或者说最后考上一所好大学?
Or eventually get into a good college?
找到份好工作 过的逍遥自在 把妹爱爱
Get a good job. Have a good lifestyle. Get laid.
我不明白为什么有人想最终患上抑郁,
I don't understand why anyone would want to end up depressed,
落得个独自一人无家可归呆在精神病房的下场
alone and homeless in a psych ward.
睡在一个叫穆塔达的自闭症患者身边
Sleeping next to some asocial reject named Muqtada.
周二
你还要挣扎多少次才肯罢休,啊?
How many times are you gonna wind up in here again, huh?
你有什么毛病啊?
What is the matter with you?
你怎么能让你的孩子看到你这副德行.啊?
How can you let your child see you like this, huh?
你这算哪门子父亲啊?
What kind of father are you?
我真觉得对她,对我们所有人来说,你还是死了的好
I honestly think it'd be better off for her, for all of us, if you were just dead.
但你连这个都做不到
But you can't even get that right.
对不起,小姐 请你离开这里
Excuse me, miss, you're going to have to leave.
走
Come on.
你还好吗,鲍比?
You okay, Bobby?
我会计
My accountant.
填错了表单然后她就疯了
Check the wrong box and the woman goes nuts.
因此,是谁在那儿买豆奶?
And so, who was there buying soy milk?
埃雷克 鲍尔温,这让我觉得挺酷的
Alec Baldwin, which I thought was kind of cool.
我和盖茨学校的招生人员谈过了
And I talked to the admissions guy at Gates.
他同意给你一个延长期
He agreed to give you an extension.
你就好好接受治疗,亲爱的 别产生任何压力,好吗?
But, you just focus on getting well, honey. Don't stress about that. Okay?
是啊,没必要产生什么压力
Uh, yeah, you shouldn't stress about it.
但也不是说这不值得努力争取
That doesn't mean it's not important to try for it.
乔治...
George...
你不是碰上了什么客户危机了吗,老爸?
Don't you have a client in crisis somewhere, Dad?
它会找上你的!
It'll come to you!
嘿,鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
面谈的怎么样?
How was your interview?
我搞砸了
I blew it.
怎么了?
What happened?
冷静!冷静!
Calm down! Calm down!
好了,兄弟 放松,放松,放松点
Okay, man. Easy, easy. Easy does it.
好了好了 没事了
Here we go. Okay. It's all right.
这让你很难受吗? 看到鲍比这样?
And was that difficult for you? Seeing Bobby like that?
我很害怕
I was scared.
不是害怕他伤害我什么的
Not that he was gonna hurt me or anything.
只是,看到一个人这样失去理智
Just, you know, seeing someone lose it like that.
让我回想起自己的感受
You know, it reminded me of how I feel sometimes.
什么感受?
How's that?
像是处在崩溃的边缘
Like I'm on the verge of just blowing up.
所有的压力紧张和焦虑开始涌现
All the stress and pressure and anxiety just bubbling up.
但我绝对不会像这样发泄出来
But I'm never able to let it out like that.
我只是把它埋藏在心底
You know, I just keep it inside.
你总是产生这种感觉吗?
Have you always felt that way?
小时候不是
Well, not when I was a kid.
跟我说说
Tell me about it.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
你记忆里感觉开心的,无忧无虑的时刻
About a time you remember being happy. Carefree.
在八年级的某一天
There was this one day back in eighth grade.
时间并不久远,但那时的时间感完全不同
It wasn't that long ago, but time felt different back then.
好像花也花不完
Like there was more of it.
我们在科尼岛玩了一个早上
We spent the morning at Coney Island.
之后,我们骑车穿过了贝里奇,
Afterwards, we rode our bikes through Bay Ridge,
日落公园
Sunset Park,
公园坡
Park Slope,
布鲁克林市中心
Downtown Brooklyn,
布鲁克林高地
Brooklyn Heights,
一直到布鲁克林大桥
all the way to the Brooklyn Bridge.
然后一切都变了
Then everything changed.
女孩,学分,父母,两场战争,
Girls, grades, parents, two wars,
迫在眉睫的环境灾难,一团糟的经济...
impending environmental catastrophe, a messed up economy...
所有的这一切似乎一股脑的冒了出来,
All these things seemed to come out of nowhere, like on the same day.
克雷格,有一句话是这样说的,
Craig, there is a saying that goes something like,
"主啊,赐予我力量去改变那些我能改变的事情,
"Lord, grant me the strength to change the things I can,
"赐予我勇气去接受那些我所不能改变的事情,
"the courage to accept the things I can't,
"并且有智慧去分别这两者的不同"
"and the wisdom to know the difference."
所以...
So...
让我们聊聊你的父母
So, let's talk about your parents.
你觉得我能改变我的父母?
You think I can change my parents?
不,但我是精神科医生
No, but I'm a psychiatrist.
所以我得问你一些关于他们的事情
So I have to ask you about them at some point.
他们都很不错
They're good people.
但是,好吧,谈谈我老爸 我今天刚见过他
But, okay, take my dad. I just saw him today.
他知道我因压力过大而入院治疗
And he knows I'm in here 'cause I'm stressed out,
但他还是提起了盖茨学校的申请
but he still brings up the Gates application.
醒醒吧,老爸
It's, like, "Get a clue, Dad.
这儿的问题更重要呢
"There's something bigger going on here."
什么问题?
And what's that?
我也不清楚
I don't know.
但是感觉很重要
But it feels big.
谢谢
Thanks.
客气
No problem.
还好吗?
Is everything okay?
还好,就是搞砸了我的面谈,没事的
Yeah, just screwing the pooch with my interview. It's okay.
我很遗憾
Oh, I'm sorry.
我已经不在乎了
I'm over it.
真的吗?
Really?
不清楚,我只是服用了安定文现在精神恍惚
Not really, I'm just zonked on Ativan.
从哪弄来的冰激凌?
Where'd you get the ice cream?
街对面的雪糕车
Mister Softee, across the street.
鲍比,老兄!
Bobby, man!
我想吃冰激凌
I want ice cream.
我能舔舔吗,鲍比?
Can I have a lick, Bob?
这要扣两分,鲍比
Got to do two points off, Bob.
很值得
It's worth it.
这些分是干吗的?
What's with these points?
是啊,这些分是干吗的?
Yeah, what is with these points?
说真的,没人可能记得清所有人的分数的
I mean, seriously, no one could possibly be keeping track of all of them.
质疑分数系统要扣三分的
That's three points off for doubting the system.
管他什么分数系统 我把分给你了
Ah, screw the system. You can have some of my points.
强尼需要舔一舔
Johnny needs a lick.
它看上去很美味
It looks good.
这是什么?
What's this?
钱
Dollar.
为了披萨派对的
For the pizza party.
- 从哪弄的? - 别管那么多了
- Where'd you get this? - Don't worry about it.
这事是真的
Yeah, it's a true story.
他是黑豹党人
He was one of the Black Panthers.
之后你再也没听到他的消息?
And you never heard from him again?
别碰我 别碰我 别碰我
Don't touch me. Don't touch me. Don't touch me.
- 别碰我 - 看到那边那位女士了吗?
- Don't touch me. - See that lady right there?
她曾是哥伦比亚大学的一名激进派学者,
She was a radical academic up at Columbia,
然后他们通过了爱国者法案
and then they passed the Patriot Act.
你知道爱国者法案吗?
You know what the Patriot Act is?
- 知道 - 好
- Yeah. - Okay.
当他们通过爱国者法案的时候,她就发了疯
When they passed the Patriot Act, then she went bonkers.
她觉得布什往所有的电话里都放了窃听器
She thought that Bush put bugs in all the phones.
很疯狂,是吧?
Pretty crazy, right?
还有那个人,所罗门,
And that guy, Solomon, over there?
他也发了疯
He's nuts, too.
他是威廉斯堡 哈西德派喜欢嗑药的群体中的一员
He's part of this Hasidic acid-head scene in Williamsburg.
所罗门可能嗑多了
他磕了100片致幻药
He did 100 tabs of acid.
别看 别看 在一个晚上
Don't look, don't look. In one night.
他是他们那圈里的第一人
And hasn't been the same since.
很疯狂,是吧?
Yeah. Crazy, right?
挺酷的
Kinda cool.
这里有些很酷的人
Some cool people in here.
那你呢?
What about you?
我什么?
What about me?
你女儿,维罗妮卡
I just...You know, um, your daughter, Veronica.
你什么时候才能再见到她?
When are you gonna see her again?
我想我女儿没有我会生活的更好
You know, I think my daughter is just better off without me.
- 别骗人了 - 没骗你,真的
- Come on. - No, really.
我并不是这儿的什么模范榜样,
I mean, I'm not really a role model in this place,
而且我觉得她只要...她就会生活的很好
and I think she's just...She's better off.
听着,我知道这不关我的事,
Look, I know that it's none of my business,
你也可以随时让我住嘴,
and you can tell me to get lost whenever you want,
我觉得她只是想让她的爸爸生活在自己身边,
but I think that she's just gonna want her dad around,
她不会去关心什么...
and I don't think she's gonna care about...
你可以打住了
You should get lost.
好吧
Okay.
安定文的药效减弱了,抱歉
I think the Ativan's wearing off, I'm sorry.
没事
It's fine.
抱歉
Sorry.
在我们越来越了解对方的时候
Do you have any other puke stories
你还有没有好笑的故事
that you'd like to share with me,
想跟我分享?
while we're getting to know each other?
我还真有几个
I have a few actually.
想玩玩吗?
Want to try?
免了
No, it's okay.
欢迎回到音乐之旅
Welcome back to musical exploration.
谁还没有乐器?
Um, who doesn't have an instrument?
太好了,兄弟 你上来当主唱
No worries, bro. Let's get you right up here on vocals.
不了,我不会唱
Uh, no, I can't sing.
就像他不会画
Like he can't draw.
真的,我...不了
Seriously, I... No, I'm just...
酷克雷格,你怕什么?上去啊
Cool Craig, what are you afraid of? Come on.
克雷格,上去 克雷格
Craig, get up there. Craig.
克雷格,克雷格,克雷格
Craig, Craig, Craig.
会唱这个吗?
You know this one?
之前好像听过
I think I've heard it before.
很好
All right.
鲍比和女士们会祝你一臂之力
Bobby and the ladies will help you out.
女士们?
The ladies?
好了,大家,就像我们上周练习的那样
Okay, people, just like we practiced last week.
准备好了吗?
You guys ready?
开始了
Here we go.
压力 把我推到
Pressure pushing down on me
把你压迫 可没人想这样
Pressing down on you no man ask for
在压力之下
Under pressure
多大的成就也会崩溃
That burns a building down
家庭因它一分为二
Splits a family in two
人们变得无家可归
Puts people on streets
但没关系
That's okay
这是在看清世界的过程中产生的恐惧
It's the terror of knowing what this world is about
看着好友们惊声尖叫 却无法逃离
Watching some good friends screaming Let me out!
只能无力的祈祷 明天会更好
Pray tomorrow gets me higher
压力折磨着人们 人们四处逃离
Pressure on people, people on the streets
别去管它了 就当你无知
Turned away from it all Like a blind man
坐在围墙之上 (好好冷静一下) 但却不起作用
Sat on a fence but it don't work
试着用爱去平息压力 但爱情是如此残酷
Keep coming up with love but it's so slashed and torn
为什么? 为什么? 为什么?
Why? Why? Why?
爱情,爱情,爱情,爱情
Love, love, love, love
疯癫的笑着 说明压力之下 我们完全变了
Insanity laughs under pressure we're cracking
我们能否再来一次?
Can't we give ourselves one more chance
为什么我们不能再给爱情一个机会
Why can't we give love that one more chance
为什么我们不能一直付出爱
Why can't we give love Give love, give love Give love, give love
一直友善相待
Give love, give love Give love, give love
爱是那么俗气的一个字
'Cause love's such an old fashioned word
爱情让你学会重新面对自己
And love dares you to change our way of
让你用更好的方式来对待自己
Caring about ourselves
这是我们的最后一曲  这才是我们自己
This is our last dance This is ourselves
压力之下
Under pressure
压力
Pressure
噢,上帝啊,你太具有明星风范了
Oh, my God, you're like a total rock star.
全学校的人都为你疯狂
Like the whole school's obsessed with you.
你现在是学校里瞩目的焦点
You're all anyone talks about anymore.
你可以考虑改变成一个新形象
You might want to think about getting a new look.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
不用担心,我们会把你弄的很酷,克雷格
Don't worry, we'll find you something cool, Craig.
酷克雷格
Cool Craig.
什么?
What?
这里有个人是这么叫我的"酷克雷格"
Oh, somebody in here calls me that. "Cool Craig."
是女的吗?
Is that somebody a girl?
噢,不是的
Uh, no.
那么,那里有没有什么漂亮的女孩?
Well, are there any cute girls in there?
不太有
Not really.
精神病院可不是什么搭讪的好地方
Like, a mental hospital probably isn't the best spot to hook up.
我真想去看看这个地方
I'm dying to see this place.
- 我能去看你吗? - 当然了
- Can I come visit? - Sure.
来吧
Yeah, you can visit.
如果你不介意我身边的狂热粉丝的话
That is if you don't mind the groupies hanging all over me.
嘿,起来
Hey, get up.
抱歉,跟你说了我很出名
Yeah, sorry, I told you I was famous.
他们又来缠我了
They were just bothering me.
你真的需要多出去活动活动了,穆塔达
You've really gotta get out of the room more, Muqtada.
外面的世界很精彩
There's a whole world out there.
周三
是我 穿上这个 我们出去走走
It's just me. Put these on. Let's go for a walk.
有时出来透透风真不错
Sometimes it's just good to get out of there.
查理,朋友
Charlie, my friend.
给你30分钟
You got 30 minutes.
嘿,你和诺艾尔算是怎么回事?
Hey, what's the deal with you and Noelle?
- 什么意思? - 什么什么意思
- What do you mean? - What do you mean, what do I mean?
别跟我装傻
Don't play dumb with me.
你们两个就像...
The two of you are like...
你的精力就像...
Your energy is like...
这是烟花
Those were fireworks.
你应该约她出去
You should ask her out.
- 约她出去? - 是的
- Ask her out? - Yeah.
约她出去 到外面去
Ask her out. Like, out.
我是喜欢她
Well, I mean, I like her,
但我太紧张了不敢约她
but I think I'd be too nervous to ask her out.
紧张什么?
What are you nervous about?
拒绝
Rejection.
亲爱的,你不能生活在恐惧之中
Babe, you can't live your life in fear.
你会变得像穆塔达一样
You're gonna end up like Muqtada.
或者更糟,像我一样
Or worse, me.
这时候你应该说,"嘿,鲍比,你的人生还没那么糟",
That's the part where you go, "Hey, Bobby, your life's not that bad," you know.
抱歉,我只是...
Oh, sorry, I'm just...
放松,没事,亲爱的
Relax. It's okay, babe.
但你不应该去担心什么拒绝
But you shouldn't worry about rejection.
你不应该 你可以先和我练习练习
You shouldn't. You can practice with me.
练习什么?
Practice what?
约诺艾尔出去
Asking Noelle out.
- 不了吧 - 我当诺艾尔
- No, that's okay. - Yeah, I'll be Noelle.
我当诺艾尔 我是诺艾尔
I'll be Noelle. I'm Noelle.
嘿,克雷格,还好吗?
Hey, Craig. How's it going?
嘿,诺艾尔 我很好 你呢?
Hey, Noelle. I'm well. How are you?
噢,也很好
Oh, good.
我很快就要离开这儿了,很不错
I get out of here soon, which is pretty cool.
你喜欢音乐吗?
Do you like music?
当然
Yeah, sure.
我喜欢现场音乐
I like live music.
你约她的时候 就准备一直坐在那儿?
Uh, you just gonna sit there the whole time you're asking her out?
站起来 我是女士
Stand up. I'm a lady.
听着哥们 你需要放松一点
No, look man. You gotta loosen up a little bit.
放松
Come on, loosen up.
很好 很好
Yeah, okay. Good, good, good.
但是我不想独自去看现场音乐
But I don't like to go see live music by myself.
噢,好吧
Oh, okay.
那么,或许我们可以一起去?
Well, maybe we could go together?
"那么,好吧,嗯,或许我们可以一起去?"
"Well, okay, uh, maybe we could go together?"
不行 再来一遍 你需要更有激情,哥们
No. Say that again. You gotta use more energy, man.
你要像这样,"噢!"你要表现的兴奋
You gotta go like, "Oh!" You gotta be excited.
好
Okay.
好啊,我们可以一起去
Yeah, uh... Yeah, okay. Well, maybe we could go together.
噢,噢,噢
Well, well, well.
我们去听谁的?
Who should we see?
U2?
不
No.
不?
吸血鬼周末?
Vampire Weekend?
不,不,不  别跟有些傻逼一样
No, no, no. Don't be one of those douchebags
带她去她不喜欢的乐队
that takes her to some band that she doesn't care about.
而你刚才就是这样,这很关键
This is what you do, and this is very important.
好
Okay.
问她喜欢什么
Ask her what she likes.
对
Right. Yeah.
- 女人喜欢被问问题 - 好的
- Women like to be asked questions. - Okay.
问我个问题 我还是扮演诺艾尔
Like ask me a question. I'll be Noelle again.
开始的时候稍微调下情
Do a little flirtation in the beginning.
什么意思?
What do you mean by that?
评价一下我的鞋
Comment on my shoes.
噢,嘿,诺艾尔 你的鞋棒极了 很上去很漂亮
Oh, hey, Noelle, those shoes are awesome. They really look nice.
噢,这么说真贴心
Oh, you're sweet to say that.
- 没什么 - 很好
- It's nothing. - Good.
说的不错  你明白过来了 你明白过来了
You got it. You're getting it. You're getting it.
- 好吧 - 还不错
- Okay. - Not bad.
你怎么会落得如此下场?
How'd you end up in here?
你是没完了,是吧?
Man, you don't give up, do you?
我在度假
I'm on vacation.
别开玩笑
Seriously.
没开玩笑
I am serious.
一些人去汉普顿 我就来这里
Some people go to the Hamptons. I come here.
到这里放松放松
Get a little R & R.
别人会照顾你
People feed you.
有时会嗑点药
I get high sometimes, man.
这不是我听说的情况
That's not what I heard about you.
你听到什么情况?
What'd you hear?
我听说你试图强奸动物园里的企鹅
I heard you tried to rape a penguin at the zoo.
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
放松点,亲爱的
Relax, babe.
挺能搞笑,啊?
Funny guy, huh?
实际上,我...
Actually, I...
我听你会计说 你曾试图自杀
I heard your accountant say that you tried to kill yourself.
或许我说的会让你感到惊讶,酷克雷格,
Well, this may come as a surprise to you, Cool Craig, but,
她不是我会计
she ain't my accountant.
天,真的?
Gee, really?
而且我曾有6次试图自杀
And I've tried to kill myself six times.
我想过这么做,但是在桥上又退缩了
I thought about doing that, but I couldn't make it to the bridge.
我就直接过来了
I just came straight here.
是什么阻止了你?
What stopped you?
我觉得,是我的家人,我父母和我妹妹
My family, I think. You know, my parents and my sister.
一想到这会对他们产生多么大的打击
Just knowing how bad it would mess them up.
看,这就是我不明白的,克雷格
See, that's the part I don't get, Craig.
你很酷,你很聪明,你很有才能
I mean, you're cool, you're smart, you're talented.
你有个爱你的家庭
You have a family that loves you.
哪怕只让我变成你一天 我会去做什么?
You know, what I would do just to be you, for just a day?
我会...我会做很多事情
I would... I would do so much.
我会...
I would...
我也不知道 我会...
I don't know. I would just...
我会活下去
I'd just live.
这有所意味
Like it meant something.
我们走
Let's go.
史密蒂,我在附近发现了这个
Smitty, I found these laying around somewhere.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
嘿,穆塔达 你要出来走走吗?
Hey, Muqtada. Are you coming out for a walk?
能干什么?
What is there to do?
喜欢画画吗?
Well, do you like to draw?
乒乓球呢
Ping-pong.
乒什么?
Ping what?
喜欢音乐吗?
You like music?
嗯
Yes.
噢,很好 那么
Okay. Great. Well, um...
只限埃及音乐
Only Egypt music.
噢,好吧,那么
Oh, well, let's see.
不好意思,能安静点吗 我要休息
Excuse me, if you please. I am trying to rest.
所罗门,进过穆塔达吗?
Sol, have you met Muqtada?
拜托能小点声吗
If you could please keep it down.
他对声音很敏感
He has sensitive hearing.
我觉得今天就这样吧
This I think is enough for one day.
嘿,克雷格
Hey, Craig.
嘿
Hey.
真是意外啊
Um, this is a surprise.
我和埃伦分手了
Me and Aaron broke up.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
抱歉
Uh, yeah. Sorry. Um...
你一定是累坏了,是吧?
You must be really loaded, huh?
嗯 我现在精疲力尽
Yeah. I'm pretty zonked.
自从前几天我们通过电话之后
So, you know I've been thinking about you non-stop
我就一直想着你
since we talked on the phone the other day.
我也经常想你
I've been thinking about you a lot, too.
我醒来之后发现我的床着了火!
I woke up and my bed was on fire!
那家伙怎么了?
What's wrong with that guy?
他有精神分裂症
He's schizophrenic.
怪异
Weird.
总之,
Anyway,
(想你是因为)你告诉我的这些事情而且你很成熟
it's like you told me all this stuff about you and you're really mature.
不像别人那些愚蠢的小问题
Not like everyone else with their stupid little problems.
你的状况真的很严重
I mean, you're really, really screwed up.
我是一团糟
I'm a mess.
但是从好的方面说  你会成长 增加阅历
But in a good way. You know, in the way that gives you experience.
那么,你和埃伦分手了?
So you and Aaron broke up?
好吧,我知道我应该想到诺艾尔,
Okay, so I know I should be thinking about Noelle,
以及我应该在20分钟之后和她见面
and how I'm supposed to be meeting her in 20 minutes.
但是当一个美丽动人的女孩在你面前,
But when you have a really gorgeous girl in front of you,
而且你已经迷恋了她两年,
and you've been obsessing over her for two years,
而且她正咬着嘴唇喃喃细语,而且你还有了反应,
and she's biting her lip and talking low, and you've got a boner,
你会怎么做?
what are you gonna do?
想看看我的房间吗?
Do you want to see my room?
你还没完成那个(申请表)吗?
You haven't finished that yet?
什么?
What?
是啊,我们这儿举办了很多活动,所以...
Yes, we have a lot of activities here, so...
占用了时间...
Takes up...
我和埃伦从没做过这种事
Me and Aaron never did anything like this.
我早就想这么做了
This was totally on my checklist.
有别人在这儿吗?
Is someone else in here?
我要吐了
I'm gonna be sick.
做爱!
Sex!
在我床上做爱!
Sex in my bed!
上帝,这真恶心
God, that's disgusting.
孩子们在我床上做爱!
Children make sex in my bed!
克雷格,这是谁?
Craig, who is this?
这是我的室友,穆塔达
Um, this is my roommate, Muqtada.
别跟她说话!
Don't talk to her!
她想要在我床上做爱
She try and make sex in my bed!
冷静 没人在做爱,好吗?
Calm down. No one was having sex, okay?
女人就是妖妇! 我就知道
Woman is temptress! I know.
- 你怎么了? - 出去
- What's wrong with you? - Get out.
他最近过的不太顺
Uh, he's going through a hard time.
不是他,是你! 你怎么了?
No, you! What's wrong with you?
我最近也过的不太顺
I'm also going through a hard time.
你应该休息了,
Um, you know what? You should get some rest,
以后再跟你联络
and I'll call you tomorrow or something.
尼娅 尼娅,等等
Nia. Nia, wait.
等等 尼娅
Wait. Nia.
我爱你
I love you.
好好歇着吧,克雷格
Just get better, Craig.
不,我...
No, I mean...
诺艾尔
Noelle.
诺艾尔,拜托了
Noelle, please.
很抱歉我搞砸了
I'm sorry I messed up.
我喜欢你的肖像 很漂亮
I love your portrait. It's amazing.
我希望你能开门
I wish you'd open the door.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
这张画的也很不错
This is pretty cool, too.
那么,刚才的事情
So, our meeting tonight.
可以当做没发生过吗?
Is it safe to assume that's not happening?
你要解决这个毛病,穆塔达
You've had it figured out all along, Muqtada.
永远离不开床
Never get out of the bed.
周四
我进去了
I got in.
进哪?
In what?
进你妈妈
In your mama.
我能到群体式家庭去住了
I got in the home.
很不错
That's great.
早餐的时候我们都很想你
We missed you at breakfast.
这是关于尼娅诺艾尔打击事件吗?
Is this about this whole NialNoelle fiasco?
你怎么知道的?
How do you know about that?
所罗门 那哥们听力很敏感
Solomon. That dude's got sensitive hearing.
听着,不仅是女人,好吗?
Look, it's not just women, okay?
我什么事都做不好 我的生活一团糟
I can't do anything right. My life's a mess.
不,我的生活一团糟
No, my life is a mess.
穆塔达的生活一团糟 无意冒犯,亲爱的
Muqtada's life is a mess. No offense, babe.
没事,老爸
All good, papa.
听着,我碰巧喜欢你,克雷格
Look, I happen to like you, Craig.
你让我回想起 我在你这个年纪的时候
You remind me of me when I was your age.
我那时更帅气,和女人交往也没这么多问题...
I was much better looking, and I didn't have as much trouble with women...
别跑题,哥们
Get back on track, man.
我要说的是,20年之后,
The point is, in 20 years,
如果你在这种地方庆祝你女儿的8岁生日,
if you're celebrating your daughter's eighth birthday in a place like this,
我对天发誓,
I swear to God,
穆塔达和我饶不了你
Muqtada and I are going to kick your ass.
如果不抓紧时间从新开始,就会一步一步陷入泥潭
He not busy being born, is busy dying.
你要相信这点
You need to believe that.
这个鲍比,
This Bobby,
是个很有智慧的人
I think, very wise man.
顺便说下,我就是来告诉你
By the way, I was just coming in to tell you that
我明天不会无家可归了
I'm not gonna be homeless tomorrow.
我就来告诉你
I'm just saying.
猜猜怎么着?
And guess what?
我隔壁就是基督教青年会
It's right next door to the YMCA.
是啊 我们就可以到游泳池游泳了,
Yeah. So we can go swimming in the swimming pool,
也可以打乒乓球
and maybe play table tennis.
乒乓,没错
Ping-pong, yes.
一个东西
It's the same thing.
听着,妈妈会在周六带你过来,
So listen, your mom will bring you by on Saturday,
我们可以举办场家庭宴会
and we could have a feast.
让我们谈谈 下午四点 老地方见
有很多人,不只是这家医院里的,
There are so many people, you know, not just in this hospital,
而是全世界的,都只是为了生存而在努力奋斗
but in the whole world, who are struggling so hard just to live.
我总是纵容自己 不懂得感激我所拥有的东西
And, it's like, self-indulgent for me to not appreciate what I have.
比如说?
Like what?
亲人,家,和朋友
Well, there's my family, my home, and my friends.
还有这个
And you know, there's this.
我过去认为艺术只不过是资产阶级的堕落象征,但是...
I used to think art was just bourgeois decadence, but...
画的真美,克雷格
It's really wonderful, Craig.
谢谢
Thanks.
我画了差不多有20幅 而且我乐在其中
Yeah, I've done about 20 of them and it's something that I really enjoy.
为什么乐在其中?
What do you enjoy about it?
因为这很有趣
It's fun.
而且它剔除了我大脑中的压力
And it takes my mind off the things that stress me out.
离开之后你也会坚持画下去吗?
You gonna continue it when you leave?
是的
Yeah.
或许吧,但是我老爸可能接受不了
Or, I think. But my dad might freak.
你跟他说过 你的感受了吗?
Have you told him how you feel?
还没有
Not yet.
但是你会的?
But you will?
是
I think so.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是我在这儿呆的最后一晚了,史密蒂
It's my last night tonight, Smitty.
是你的最后一晚,克雷格
It is your last night, Craig.
我其实不想告诉你的,克雷格,你走了我会想你的
I hate to break it to you, Craig, but I think I'm really gonna miss you.
这也是鲍比的最后一晚,
Well, it's Bobby's last night, too,
所以 我想知道我们能不能举办一场披萨派对
so I was wondering if we could have a pizza party.
当然可以 你们有钱吗? 有钱就行
Yes, we can. Yeah. Do you have the money? If you can get the money.
我会弄到钱的
Yeah, no, I'll have the money. Yeah, I...
能带些唱片吗?
You have records you could bring?
嘿,谢谢你能来
Hey, thanks for coming.
衣服上写着 我恨男孩
我就是想说,我对昨天发生的事情感到抱歉
I just wanted to say, I'm really sorry about what happened yesterday.
那个和我一起的女孩,她是我死党的女朋友
That girl I was with, she's my best friend's girlfriend.
我一直迷恋着她而且...
I've been obsessed with her forever and...
而且你爱上她了?
And you're in love with her?
没有
No.
噢,当然没有了,但是你觉得她很性感,
Well, of course not. But you think she's hot,
所以你就跟她说了 你认为她想听到的话
so you told her what you thought she'd want to hear.
现在你又要把这招用到我身上
And now you're going to do the same thing to me.
不,不是的
No, I'm not.
不是?
You're not?
听着,你是很性感,
Look, um, I do think you're hot.
而且我也想说好听的话,
And I do want to say the right thing,
但这只是因为我喜欢你
but that's only because I really like you.
我喜欢 你不像别人那样掩饰自己的问题
I like how you don't hide your problems like everyone else.
而且我觉得在你身边的时候,我也不必隐瞒自己的缺陷
And I feel like I don't have to hide mine when I'm around you.
我最近经常考虑这件事,
You know, I've been thinking about it a lot recently,
我意识到 如果你不抓紧时间从新开始,你就会一步一步陷入泥潭
and I've realized that if you're not busy being born, you're busy dying.
而我,作为其中之一,认为我们从新开始是个双赢的局面
And I, for one, think that we could both benefit from being born, again.
不是指再次出生,你明白我的意思是吧?
Not being born again, but you know what I mean?
天,谢谢你的箴言,鲍勃
Gee, thanks for the wisdom, Bob.
什么?他也告诉你了?
What? He told you that, too?
谁?鲍比
Who? Bobby.
是啊,告诉了我和一大群人
Yeah, me and about a billion other people.
鲍勃 迪伦
Bob Dylan.
你说的是他的歌的歌词
It's the song you just quoted.
- 什么? 不 - 是的
- What? No. - Yes.
总而言之,我的重点是
Anyway, my point is
我想和你玩医生游戏
I want to play doctor with you.
这太美了
This is awesome.
你怎么从没问过我为什么?
So, how come you never asked me why?
什么为什么?
Why what?
我觉得 你想告诉我时自然会告诉我
I guess I just assumed you'd tell me when you wanted me to know.
谢谢
Thanks.
你喜欢音乐吗?
Do you like music?
你喜欢呼吸吗?
Do you like breathing?
是啊 真是个愚蠢的问题
That's right. It was a dumb question.
我...我很喜欢电台司令,Pixies和T. Rex
I like... I like Radiohead a lot, the Pixies, T. Rex.
噢,还有什么来着?
Oh, what else?
看过他们的现场演出吗?
Have you seen them live?
看过一次电台司令和Pixies的
I saw Radiohead and the Pixies once.
酷
Cool.
吸血鬼周末乐队这个月底有一场演出
You know, Vampire Weekend's doing a show at the end of the month.
你想去吗?
Would you want to go?
当然了
Yes, I would.
和你一起,对吧?
With you, right?
不,和所罗门一起
No, with Solomon.
当然是和我一起了
Yeah, with me.
抱歉大伙儿
Sorry guys.
场面开始变得戏剧化,
This is about to get pretty sappy,
所以我只展示出其中的关键点
so I'm just gonna give you the highlights.
这是我在发表
This is me sharing the realization that
我其实并不想当什么CEO,律师,或者总统的言论
I don't actually want to be a CEO, lawyer, or President.
这是诺艾尔,
This is Noelle,
嘲笑我曾想过要当总统这个想法
laughing at the idea that I once wanted to be President.
这是诺艾尔提议 如果申请盖茨暑假学校让我很烦恼
Here, Noelle suggests I "screw"
我就"去他妈的去吧"
the Gates Summer application if it makes me so unhappy.
这是我喜欢这个主意
This is me liking that idea.
这是我在考虑怎样告诉我老爸
This is me thinking about how to tell my dad.
这是我告诉诺艾尔 我觉得她有多漂亮之后
This is after I tell Noelle how beautiful I think she is.
来自Argenon医院的问候
就让他们转告送货员让他到三楼
Okay, just have them send the delivery guy to the third floor.
三楼北区
3 North.
没问题,老兄 交给我了
No problem, sport. You got it.
- 谢谢,老爸 - 应该的
- Thanks, Dad. - Sure.
我明天就能见到你和妈妈了
Yeah, I'll see you and Mom tomorrow.
到时见
I'll see you then.
- 好的,拜 - 拜拜
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
嘿,穆塔达
Hey, Muqtada.
- 喂? - 嘿,哥们
- Hello? - Hey, man.
我需要帮助
I could really use a favor.
嘿,找到了
Hey, found it.
太感谢了
I so appreciate this.
啊,没事
Yeah, no problem.
听着,哥们,很抱歉之前对你那么凶
Look, man, I'm sorry I was a bitch to you.
很抱歉我试图和你女朋友亲热
I'm sorry I tried to make out with your girlfriend.
和尼娅怎么样了?
How are things with Nia?
还在磨合吧
Um, we're gonna try and work through it.
很好
Good.
知道吗,我掩饰的很好,但是
You know, I might hide it pretty well, but,
我有时也会消沉沮丧之类的
I mean, I get that depression stuff, too, sometimes.
是吗?
Yeah?
别伤害你自己,好吗?
Don't kill yourself, okay?
不会的
I won't.
我是认真的
Seriously.
谢谢
Thanks.
明天再打给你,好吗?
I'll call you tomorrow, all right?
好的
Yeah, you will.
你真曾试图和尼娅亲热吗?
Did you really try to make out with Nia?
混蛋
Dick.
披萨要凉了 怎么了?
Pizza's getting cold. What's up?
我累了,老兄
I'm tired, man.
估计我要错过这场披萨狂欢了
Think I'll skip out on the pizza shin-dig.
打包呢
Pack up.
度假结束了
Ah, vacation's over.
是啊,该回去工作了
Yes, back to work.
- 你还有工作? - 没有
- You got a job? - No.
恭喜你有房子住了
Well, congratulations on your home.
谢谢
Thanks.
我对诺艾尔说了那些迪伦的歌词
You know, I used that Dylan line on Noelle.
效果怎么样?
How'd it go?
很好 我们约好了一起出去玩儿
Good. We're gonna hang out soon.
- 是吗? - 看一些音乐会什么的
- Yeah? - Maybe see some music.
很好
Good.
给
Here.
是你
It's you.
哎呦 上面一团糟,哥们
Yikes. It's a mess in there, man.
并不是特别糟
Oh, it's not such a mess.
只不过是在整修而已
It's just undergoing renovations.
我在后面写上了我的电话
Look, I wrote my number on the back.
我们应该时不时的出来聚聚,打打乒乓球
We should get together sometime, play some table tennis.
当然
Sure.
很好 明天早餐再见了
Cool. Well, I'll see you tomorrow at breakfast.
祝你好运,克雷格
Good luck, Craig.
并不是你需要它,只是...
Not that you need it, but...
谢谢 你也是,亲爱的
Thanks. You, too, babe.
嘿,不是吧
Hey, come on.
相信我
Trust me.
我还要跳舞
I gotta dance.
不好意思?
Excuse me?
我喜欢这个
I like this.
看
Look.
周五
再见了,兄弟
So long, buddy.
你应该再多呆一会
You should probably stay longer.
你在外面可能会再次失控的
You might lose it on the outside.
我宁愿试一试
Um, I'll take my chances.
它会找到你的!
It'll come to you!
我知道你在想,"这算什么?
Okay, I know you're thinking, "What is this?
"一孩子在医院呆了几天 然后所有的问题就都解决了?"
"Kid spends a few days in the hospital and all his problems are cured?"
但是我没有 我知道我还没有
But I'm not. I know I'm not.
我能感觉到这只是个开始
I can tell this is just the beginning.
我仍然要去面对作业,学校,朋友
I still need to face my homework, my school, my friends.
老爸
My dad.
你好,史密蒂
Hello, Smitty.
感谢你所做的一切
Thanks for everything.
不用客气,先生
Sure. You're very welcome, sir.
看到鲍比了吗?
Have you seen Bobby around?
嗯,鲍比一大早就走了
Yeah, Bobby left pretty early this morning.
但是今天和上周六的区别
But the difference between today and last Saturday
是头一次的,
is that for the first time in a while,
我能抱着积极的眼光 去追求那些我想要做的事情
I can look forward to the things I want to do in my life.
感觉怎么样?
How you feeling?
感觉...
I feel like...
没问题
Like I can handle it.
骑车,吃饭,喝水,聊天
Bike, eat, drink, talk.
乘地铁,读书,看地图
Ride the subway, read, read maps.
画地图,搞艺术
Make maps, make art.
终结盖茨学校申请
Finish the Gates application.
告诉老爸不要因此产生压力
Tell my dad not to stress about it.
拥抱老妈,亲吻小妹
Hug my mom. Kiss my little sister.
亲吻老爸
Kiss my dad.
和诺艾尔亲热
Make out with Noelle.
继续和她亲热
Make out with her more.
带她去野餐 和她一起看电影
Take her on a picnic. See a movie with her.
和埃伦一起看电影 噢,和尼娅一起看电影
See a movie with Aaron. Heck, see a movie with Nia.
参加聚会 告诉别人我的故事 在三楼北区做志愿者
Have a party. Tell people my story. Volunteer at 3 North.
帮助像鲍比一样的人
Help people like Bobby.
像穆塔达一样的人
Like Muqtada.
像我一样的人
Like me.
继续画画 画一个人 画一个裸体的人
Draw more. Draw a person. Draw a naked person.
画诺艾尔的裸体
Draw Noelle naked.
跑步,旅行,游泳,蹦着走
Run, travel, swim, skip.
是啊,我知道这很挫,但是,管他呢
Yeah, I know it's lame, but, whatever.
我就要蹦
Skip anyway.
平心定气
Breathe.
享受人生
Live.
字幕翻译&制作 真喜